[
    {
        "question": "A customer relationship management (CRM) application runs on Amazon EC2 instances in multiple Availability Zones behind an Application Load Balancer.\n\nIf one of these instances fails, what occurs?",
        "answer": "The load balancer will stop sending requests to the failed instance"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company needs to perform asynchronous processing, and has Amazon SQS as part of a decoupled architecture. The company wants to ensure that the number of empty responses from polling requests are kept to a minimum.\n\nWhat should a solutions architect do to ensure that empty responses are reduced?",
        "answer": "Increase the receive message wait time for the queue"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company currently stores data for on-premises applications on local drives. The chief technology officer wants to reduce hardware costs by storing the data in Amazon S3 but does not want to make modifications to the applications. To minimize latency, frequently accessed data should be available locally.\n\nWhat is a reliable and durable solution for a solutions architect to implement that will reduce the cost of local storage?",
        "answer": "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway configured in cached volume mode"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company runs a public-facing three-tier web application in a VPC across multiple Availability Zones. Amazon EC2 instances for the application tier running in private subnets need to download software patches from the internet. However, the instances cannot be directly accessible from the internet.\n\nWhich actions should be taken to allow the instances to download the needed patches? (TWO actions)",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Configure a NAT gateway in a public subnet"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Define a custom route table with a route to the NAT gateway for internet traffic and associate it with the private subnets for the application tier"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A solutions architect wants to design a solution to save costs for Amazon EC2 instances that do not need to run during a 2-week company shutdown. The applications running on the instances store data in instance memory (RAM) that must be present when the instances resume operation.\n\nWhich approach should the solutions architect recommend to shut down and resume the instances?",
        "answer": "Run the applications on instances enabled for hibernation. Hibernate the instances before the shutdown"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company plans to run a monitoring application on an Amazon EC2 instance in a VPC. Connections are made to the instance using its private IPv4 address. Asolutions architectneeds to design a solution that will allow traffic to be quickly directed to a standby instance if the application fails and becomes unreachable.\n\nWhich approach will meet these requirements?",
        "answer": "Attach a secondary elastic network interface (ENI) to the instance configured with the private IP address. Move the ENI to the standby instance if the primary instance becomes unreachable"
    },
    {
        "question": "An analytics company is planning to offer a site analytics service to its users. The service will require that the users’ web pages embed a JavaScript file that is hosted in the company’s Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhat must a solutions architectdo to ensure that the script will successfully execute?",
        "answer": "Enable cross-origin resource sharing (CORS)on the S3 bucket"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company’s security team requires that all data stored in the cloud be encrypted at rest at all times using encryption keys stored on-premises.\n\nWhich encryption options meet theserequirements? (TWO encryption options)",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Use Server-Side Encryption with CustomerProvided Keys (SSE-C)"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Use client-side encryption to provide at-rest encryption"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A company needs tomaintain access logs for a minimum of 5 yearsdue to regulatory requirements. The data is rarely accessed once stored, but must be accessible with oneday’s notice if it is needed.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective data storage solution that meets these requirements?",
        "answer": "Store the data in Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive storage and delete the objects after 5years using a lifecycle rule"
    },
    {
        "question": "A company uses Reserved Instances to run its data-processing workload. The nightly job typically takes 7 hours to run and must finish within a 10-hour time window. The company anticipates temporary increases in demand at the end of each month that will cause the job to run over the time limit with the capacity of the current resources. Once started, the processing job cannot be interrupted before completion. The company wants to implement a solution that would allow it toprovide increased capacity as cost-effectively as possible.\n\nWhat should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
        "answer": "Deploy On-Demand Instances during periods of high demand"
    }
]